koware souna boku no kokoro
Though my spirit may be broken,
yasashiku tsutsumi konde
It's bound tightly with kindness.
kimi wa warau madamada akirameru ni wa hayai yoto
When you laugh, I just can't give up so quickly.
mou sukoshi ganbareru hara
If I can carry on a little more,
mune hareru sono hi made
Stretch myself until that day,
mabuta tojite goran
What I should see when I close my eyes
kagayaku kimi kitto mieru hazu
Will surely be you shining there.
fuminarase yo daichi wo
Stamp your feet on the ground
tashikana yume idaite
And sincerly embrace your dream.
ano sora ni kakageta omoi wa
Your thoughts will carry through the sky.
imademo made soredemo made
Still, even now, and still, even so,
sono te ni nokotte imasuka
Are you sure it stayed in your hand?
jounetsu yo maiagare ima
Let your passion rise now,
zetsubou wo kibou to kaeru made
Untill your despair becomes hope.
ougon no chigai moetsukiru koto naku
Get yourself fired up with a golden vow,
hibi kimi wa
And every day
owari naki chousen
You can face a challenge without end.
RUN AND RUN. . . .
mata nandodemo hashiri tsuzukeru
However long it takes you, keep running.
yumeoibito wa tuku namae wa iranai
mezashite yuku yo Wonderland