The dreams that I drew are appearing before my eyes,
as I stand here comparing these two scenes in front of me
Their shape begins to change, and I find that here and now.
There is only one single thing that I know.
Spring passed through,
I reluctantly saw it go.
Our opening act took place that summer.
I began to understand all sorts of things.
Fall passed and we lost something over the winter.
And in a mountain of trash,
I search for that dream I had.
Hear my voice now.
Hear it from my heart now.
Until my tears, all dry away...
I'll keep running after the answer.
Until my tears, all clear away...
The place where I will be,
even as I hesitate,
is here drawing out a new future.
Chiseling...
Proving it...
With these two hands!
Who are you?
You are Honda Goro-kun, Right?
Yes, I am.
My name is Kusakabe.
I came here on behalf of the major leaguer, Joe Gibson
Gibson?!
An invitation from Gibson
Your mother was?
It wasn't serious,
but she's staying at the hospital for one night just to be on the safe side.
What a time to visit here...
So, what does Gibson want?
He wanted me to give this to you.
They're plane and invitational tickets to the Major League All Star Game.
Major All Star?!
Yes.
Of course, Gibson will make his appearance too.
Since you are on summer break, would you like to come with your mother?
If you feel unsure, I can come along and...
There is no reason for me to accept this.
Goro-kun...
We have no relationship with each other.
Why does he have to do this now?
It's true that he took away your father's life.
So it's natural that you hate him.
But that's why...
I don't hate him.
He must think that killing my father was only another unfortunate event.
That's not true!
He was...
He's trying to make up after things have cooled down.
Listen, Goro-kun.
Do you think we'll be happier with just this?
He didn't even show up at Dad's funeral!
That's not it!
He's not...
Gibson is not that kind of man.
It was the day of your father's funeral.
Gibson is not here?!
What have you been doing?!
I'm sorry!
I told him the time and the place...
Make sure to find him!
It will be a scandal if he doesn't come.
Yes.
Did you hear that?
Gibson is skipping out on the funeral.
I guess when you get as good as Gibson, killing a man isn't a big deal.
I searched for Gibson everywhere.
And...
I finally found him.
Mister, what do you think you're doing?!
Mark told me about this,
and I've been wanting to play it.
It sure is an exciting game.
It's the day of Honda's Funeral!
Come with me!
Please go in place of me.
I saw his corpse yesterday.
That's enough!
You have an obligation to attend the funeral!
You should know that.
The cause of his death was your ball...
Your throwing hand...
I know that.
I took away Honda's father with my left arm.
But what can I say at the funeral?
What kind of face do I need to make?
How can I apologize to that crying Honda boy?
Tell me, Kusakabe.
Gibson...
After that, Gibson didn't play for a month. The reason reported was back pain.
But it was really because of that injury.
His contract was for one year.
But you know how he stayed for three years?
That was his way of making up for it.
For the Japanese baseball scene who lost Honda, and for his family.
He often said,
there's nothing I can do but show as many Japanese kids as possible the Major League pitches.
Goro-kun,
on the plane ticket's envelope,
there is his own hand writing. he wrote...
"To Shigenaru Junior"
"I will give this to the son of Mr.Honda,"
"the greatest slugger I have ever met in my baseball career"
Game invitation from Gibson?
The plane tickets and a hotel voucher for two nights as well.
These tickets are for first class,
and the hotel is a good one too.
How much money do you think he makes each year?
That's pocket change to him.
But I can't go.
I just got released now.
I know the interpreter will be with you, but America is so...
I'm worried that something might happen to you.
I want to go!
I want to go there, and watch the Major League.
I want to see the best pitchers and batters of the country that created the game of baseball.
We'd better go get you a passport.
Yay!
Hey, that's my bag!
Here it comes!
Yeah.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Do you think we can win against Yokohama Little like that?
We can't win either way.
But Honda-kun looks like he's serious.
Jeez, be more serious!
I am!
But the paper ball is so bumpy, so it bounces irregularly!
Besides, I don't have a mitt.
Do it yourself if you can!
Oh...
Good one.
The irregular bounce forces you into the habit of watching the ball up until the last moment.
And we'd better get used to catching without a glove.
Man, we'll be spending the entire summer break like this.
Oh, speaking of summer break...
Traveling to America?!
Honda-kun, wasn't Gibson, the guy who sent you the tickets...
Oh, yeah, your dad...
I don't mind that anymore.
My mom is still recovering, so she can't go.
So there is one extra ticket.
Gulp...
No way!
Serouisly?!
So, let's go together, Komori
Me?
Honda-kun?!
Why are you excluding us after getting us excited?
Because you don't know baseball.
You'll be bored watching the Major League.
But that's still not fair.
You are one good man, Komori!
Well, fine.
Then we'll use Rock, Paper, Scissors.
All right!
Rock, Paper...
Check it out, Honda!
The buildings are so small!
Sir, should we kick her out at the next station?
Hurry! Hurry! Honda!
We are here!
It's America everywhere!
Wake up, Honda!
The sky is so blue!
Shut up!
It's 5 o'clock in the morning in Japan right now!
Sir, what's that?
It's the Golden Gate Parks Stadium.
That's the home ground of the Guardians the team Gibson plays on.
So is Gibson's house around here?
Yeah.
Do you want to go see him?
I didn't come here to see him.
I just came to watch the Major League.
Wow!
Super rich!
Your room is the next one, Shimizu-san.
I'm sorry, but I need to go out for a bit.
I have a recruiting meeting.
Oh, yeah.
You are the interpreter for the Warriors.
I'll be back around 8:00 for dinner.
Do not go out of the room.
The room is extravagant but...
There's nothing to do.
We're all by ourselves.
I know. All alone...
Oh, yeah , the TV!
What kind of shows do they have?
Would there be any Japanese subtitles?
Of course not.
Excuse me.
Answer it, Honda!
No way! You answer it!
It might be the interpreter!
I'm sorry!
The meeting got long.
You're late, man.
Are you hungry?
I have a dinner reservation.
I was about to go to bed too.
It's Gibson.
What is he saying?
It sounds like it's about tomorrow's game.
"I'm honored to be a part of the all star game."
"I don't know if I'll be the starting pitcher,"
"but I will do my best for all my fans in this country,"
"and for my friends who came all the way from Japan."
Goro-kun, Gibson stopped by earlier to give this to you.
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Wel
come
to
Ame
rica
Good morning, Japanese fans.
The dream game of baseball fans around the glove, the Major League All Star Game is about to begin.
Everything here is so big.
But it's so far up from the field, I can't see the players' expressions.
So, how does it feel to be at the Major's stadium, Goro-kun?
Nothing much.
The artificial grass is pretty,
but I got more excited when I went to the Oceans Stadium for the first time.
Is that so?
That's pretty.
Fireworks are prettier in Japan.
You party pooper!
You've been whining all this time
If it's that boring, go back to Japan now!
You're the one who made it boring!
You've done this to my arm!
Well, that was...
OUCH!
You're so annoying.
I apologized so many times!
Besides, you have a dirty mind, trying to hug me, even if I looked so damn cute in my sleep.
Oh, come on.
But it was lucky that it wasn't your throwing arm.
Besides, it was only a minor crack.
Oh, stand up, both of you.
The opening ceremony is about to start.
"I will do my best for my friends from Japan."
The game is about to begin.
On the mound is Freddy Marks, with the most strike outs in the Southern League.
Facing him is the star first batter of the Northern League, Steve Sommers.
He hits the first pitch!
Out!
Good one.
Japanese players wouldn't be able to do that so easily
Burns hits a big one!
The ball flies to deep right field!
The fast dasher, Burns heads for the second base!
Second baseman will relay the ball...
No, he doesn't!
Out!
It's a laser beam!
Bret Faulkner's lightning fast return!
Offence and defense are both playing their best!
This is Major!
What do you think, Goro-kun?
It finally feels like I'm in America
The top of the first, Northern League ended their turn with no score.
Now, the bottom of the inning.
On the mound will be the man all you Japanese fans are familiar with.
Currently, he has 10 wins and 1 loss. His ERA is 0.98.
It's Joe Gibson!
I'm glad you made it, Boy.
I'll give you the best show.
Play!
And here is the first pitch!
Strike!
He starts with a 153 km/h fastball.
He sure is fast.
Pitchers who can throw at over 150 km/h are hard to come by even here.
Strike!
He swings and misses!
And it was 154 km/h
Use split finger, to the same place as the first pitch.
Then curve?
No!
In this game, I will only pitch fastballs!
What was that?
It looked like Gibson just said something.
He'll only use fastballs in this game?
Damn him!
Strike out!
The fastball...
What was that?
Wilder strikes out, swinging at the high speed pitch.
Gibson must have said he will only use fastballs.
This just came in.
Gibson declared that he will only pitch fastballs in this game.
Strike! Batter out!
Jose strikes out!
A 154 km/h fastball!
Just like when he pitched against your father.
The better his opponents are, the more particular Gibson gets about using his fastballs.
And your father homered his 160 km/h.
He might be trying to prove how great your father was...
by striking the Major leaguers out with only fastballs.
Yes, only to you.
Strike out!
Martin is struck out!
Using only fastballs, as he declared Gibson has struck out the Northern League's top rotation.
Strike out!
Lucas, MVP for the last two years, strikes out as well!
That's 4 strike outs in a row!
One more to tie the All Star record!
Doing such a feat still won't...
It still doesn't...
Strike out!
Faulkner was struck out too!
He has tied the record!
And there it is! 100 miles! 160 km/h!
Unbelievable...
One more to go.
Will he break the record?
Gibson is very fired up today.
Honda.
Hey,
do you think I can see Gibson after the game?
Let's see, this one for Komori.
15 dollars? How much is that?
The Northern League won 3-2 this year.
But Gibson's consecutive strike outs is the biggest news this year.
Ah. There he is.
You've gotten big, Kid.
I thought I needed to say thanks for the invitation.
Also, I wanted to ask you something.
It really was an accident, right?
Goro-kun!
Of course it was!
The ball just slipped and...
I didn't ask you!
Come on, Boy.
I'm done!
What's going on?
His answer to you is this:
Even if it was an accident, it was the fault of my skill and mental immaturity.
There is nothing to excuse me from
the sin of killing your father.
If this can make you feel any better, throw this from the mound to me as hard as you can.
This is about all I can do right now.
I like that.
I can finally have revenge with my own hand.
Goro-kun!
Honda!
Stop that!
What good does it do?!
Damn, I lacked control because of my left arm.
This is not fair.
A grade schooler's pitch won't hurt that much, no matter what happens.
Let's postpone this punishment game
until some other time
Untill I can pitch as good as you.
Good bye, Mister.
See you again, Boy
This wind feels so good.
I was timid, but am pushing forward...
to the beginning of my dreams!
I'm going to meet a mysterious challenger tomorrow.
That's the image I embrace even when I'm sleeping.
I think I'll wear some normal clothes.
I'm all here this morning.
If you believe, your dream's supposed to come true.
That's what we all believe, but...
what will you do today to believe?
And as the door opens...
The noisy trees
strike my ears suddenly.
And that's the introduction to my dreams.
The hurdles are in my heart.
I leap over them one by one.
Heading to the final goal of my dreams.
Next Episode
We decided to have a traning camp to prepare for the fall tournament.
It's a joint camp site where many strong teams from the area congregate.
I can't wait to see who will be there!
Next: Major - The Summer! The Baseball! The Training Camp!
Head for the stage of your dreams!
The Summer! The Baseball!
The Training Camp!