Truth is elusive, it's nowhere to be found
Yeah, the truth can never be written
Down, it's not in any magazine, you can't see
It on your TV screen
Truth is evasive, though you might have the facts
Got it straight, you think but then it all
Cracks wide open, you can search the world far and wide
The only truth that you can ever find
Is in another,
A soul that's got the same burning need
To find out what's 'neath the cover up
The one can't be without the true other
So let's get together, see what we can uncover
One that defines your world, gives you truth and life
One that excels,
special enough to guide your way through
The shadow world